<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: BOSS | BOSS Hack-A-Thon]]></title>
  <link href="http://bosshack.org/blog/categories/boss/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bosshack.org/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-18T08:16:45-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://bosshack.org/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[BOSS]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planning Meetup Summary]]></title>
    <link href="http://bosshack.org/blog/2012/12/17/planning-meetup-summary/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-17T20:21:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://bosshack.org/blog/2012/12/17/planning-meetup-summary</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>%p So the Google Hangout formula seemed to work out for this planning meetup.  I've embedded it at the bottom of this post.</p>

<p>%p
  We talked about quite a few things.  It was agreed upon that we'd expect to see
  a list of projects with sponsors, and that in general there'd only be one project
  per sponsor.  Then anyone who was interested in that project could sign on and say
  "yeah, I'd like to help with that."  That's pretty much all of the rigor that will
  go into figuring out the projects ahead of time - we'll organize online and hopefully
  have a good feel for what we're doing by the time that we arrive.</p>

<p>%p
  I've updated the
  %a{:href => '/first-hackathon-nominations/index.html'} potential projects
  list to reflect newly suggested projects.  If someone feels that a project is dead,
  feel free to submit a PR with it removed.  If you want a project added, send a PR
  with the new project (or mention it in a comment and we can help out).</p>

<p>%p Within a week or so, we should remove projects that haven't had a champion yet.  If you'd like to nominate yourself as a champion for a given project, either send a PR with yourself listed on the project on this page, or mention it in comments (lazy) and we'll put it up there for you.</p>

<p>%iframe{ width:560, height:315, src:"http://www.youtube.com/embed/wACXOEF2dRQ", frameborder:"0", allowfullscreen: true }</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOSS Hack planning meetup]]></title>
    <link href="http://bosshack.org/blog/2012/12/11/boss-hack-planning-meetup/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-11T12:06:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://bosshack.org/blog/2012/12/11/boss-hack-planning-meetup</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>%table.event-info
  %tr</p>

<pre><code>%td.label
  %strong Date/Time
%td.info 6pm 17-Dec-2012
</code></pre>

<p>  %tr</p>

<pre><code>%td.label
  %strong Location
%td.info
  %a{:href =&gt; "https://plus.google.com/u/0/events/clkj95bn5ft5nge19ggfonpgodc"}Google Hangout
  or
  %a{:href =&gt; "http://isotope11.com/contact"}isotope | eleven Offices
</code></pre>

<p>  %tr</p>

<pre><code>%td.label
  %strong Signup
%td.info
  %a{:href =&gt; "http://www.meetup.com/bhamboss/events/92753442/"}Meetup
</code></pre>

<p>%br/</p>

<p>%p
  BOSS will hold it's December meetup at 6pm CST on 17-Dec, 2012.  Since the holidays are so near and many of our regular attendees
  have a busy social calendar this meeting will be via Google Hangout.
  %a{:href => 'https://github.com/knewter'}Josh
  has scheduled the
  %a{:href => "https://plus.google.com/u/0/events/clkj95bn5ft5nge19ggfonpgodc"}hangout
  so click the link to get a reminder.
%p
  Participation in the hangout is optional.  Members that prefer to attend the meeting at the
  %a{:href => "http://isotope11.com/contact"}isotope | eleven Offices
  are encoraged to do so.</p>

<p>%p
  Our adgenda for this meeting will be:
  %ul</p>

<pre><code>%li
  Planning the logistics for the
  %a{:href =&gt; "http://bosshack.org/blog/2012/11/27/first-boss-hack-a-thon-scheduled/"}Hack-A-Thon
%li
  Reviewing the current list of project
  %a{:href =&gt; "http://bosshack.org/first-hackathon-nominations/index.html"}nominations
%li
  Whatever else comes up...
</code></pre>

<p>%p
  As is the case with any hacker meeting, familiarity with the technology involved (Google Hangout)
  is encouraged.  You may desire to share your screen, mute your audio, or put a mustache on your image.
  Be Prepared....</p>

<p>%h1 Hope to see you on Monday!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First BOSS Hack-A-Thon Scheduled]]></title>
    <link href="http://bosshack.org/blog/2012/11/27/first-boss-hack-a-thon-scheduled/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-27T21:38:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://bosshack.org/blog/2012/11/27/first-boss-hack-a-thon-scheduled</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>%p Birmingham Open Source Software has scheduled our first Hack-A-Thon for 26-Jan-2013, also known as the last Saturday in January, 2013.</p>

<p>%p
  Several
  %a{:href => '/first-hackathon-nominations/index.html'}potential projects
  were suggested at our last BOSS meetup.  This list will most likely grow, so make sure you check back often.   Additional nominations
  are encouraged - just post your suggestions in the comments</p>

<p>%p
  We're planning on having a virtual meeting in December to nail down the details.   Date and time of the December meeting
  will be posted on the
  %a{:href => 'http://www.meetup.com/bhamboss/'}BOSS Meetup Page</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
